#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/matthew-hall-nyc (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS) Serverless Computing Database Development

#### Honors-Awards

Simon School of Business -Scholarship Weekend Candidate

# **Matthew Hall**

Machine Learning, DevOps, Finance Rochester, New York, United States

### Summary

I am a highly motivated and creative individual who can tackle complex analytical problems and turn data into actionable insights to directly solve business problems. I have entrepreneurial experience working in multiple startups, ranging from industries of fashion to FinTech, and seafood supply chain. During my time at Simon Business School, I've been a Python Data Science trainer, running weekly technical seminars, while also being a Graduate Teaching Assistant and Tutor.

Tools of Choice: Python, R, SQL, Machine Learning, Neural Networks

## Experience

Corning Incorporated 1 year 11 months

Software Engineer, MLOps and Advanced Analytics September 2022 - Present (8 months) Corning, New York, United States

Emerging Technologies, Value Acceleration

Machine Learning Engineer I, Finance April 2022 - September 2022 (6 months) Corning, New York, United States

Finance Analyst - Advanced Analytics June 2021 - April 2022 (11 months) Corning, New York, United States

#### **Pharos Seafood**

Data Science - Industry Research & Data Mining January 2021 - June 2021 (6 months) Warwick, Rhode Island, United States

University of Rochester - Simon Business School Graduate Teaching Assistant and Tutor January 2021 - May 2021 (5 months)

Rochester, New York, United States

TA for Pricing Analytics & Python/R Tutor

Alas Mgt
Co-Founder / VP DevOps Engineer
October 2019 - June 2020 (9 months)
New York, New York

MaxW Funding
Sales And Marketing Specialist
June 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 5 months)
New York, New York

Matthew Hall Productions, LLC Founder & Photographer / Filmmaker October 2016 - September 2019 (3 years) New York, New York

### Education

University of Rochester - Simon Business School Master of Science - MS, Finance · (2020 - 2021)

New York University
Bachelor's degree, Business & Social Sciences · (2016 - 2020)